This is Trigun.
guitar solo
This video is brought
to you by
R .I
.P.
What a pleasant surprise.
A fortuitous occasion indeed,
just who I wanted to see.
You're angry with me, aren't you?
Apparently you're unhappy that
I forced you to kill Nicholas D.
Wolfwood.
Your scene is over now, Chapel.
Now the curtain will
rise for the final act.
I'm curious.
Why did you come here?
I don't know how to live without
being able to pay off a debt.
That's nonsense.
Animals run instinctively
when they sense danger.
But your behavior is
completely irrational.
Your sacrifice is meaningless.
You don't even deserve
to be called a fool.
The only reason the human
race came to possess
the capability of
compassion and a sense of
moral was because they
somehow mistakenly believed
themselves to be a
superior breed of beast.
The moment they taste the fear of
knowing there's a superior breed,
something seems to take
control over them every time.
And for some reason, humans act
merely by instinct from that point on.
The cornered mouse attacks the cat,
even knowing the cat has the upper hand.
But the cat was wise to the mouse's game.
The mouse seeks death in
order to avoid the pain.
Imagine the place between life and death.
Yes, the pain you feel
is your very essence.
The essence of the human
animal known as homo sapien.
AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH
Garbage,
only good for consuming resources.
Hmph.
I understand.
Master, vas the stampede will
experience eternal pain and suffering.
$5,000! $5,000! Get down here!
$5,000!
$5,000! $5,000! Hey, lady!
Oh, miss, may I have some donuts, please?
Oh, yeah?
How many do you want?
$30 double dollars worth!
Oh, and could you please
make them fresh ones?
I don't want any day olds, okay?
Fine, yeah, whatever, don't worry!
Mm-hmm.
A populated city at last.
Sure feels good to see
happy people around again.
It's a lucky, lucky day.
Bonjour, je t 'aime.
Mm.
That smells great.
What a heavenly aroma.
Smells like little cakes made from honey.
And without further ado...
This is incredible.
Super tasty.
It's so good to be alive!
Come back!
She's gonna buy us some new toys!
Have you been to Maggie's store?
She has new bolts of that
nice fabric you like so much.
I had no idea.
Thanks a lot!
I'll help you out.
Which girl is she?
Never mind, I'll go tell her myself.
At least tell me for me.
It takes three days to get there
by sand steaming. Forget it!
Trust me, you've got absolutely
nothing to worry about.
It'll be fine.
All right, you say so.
I'll tell you what, I'm
gonna get you for that.
These are good.
These are really good.
But why are these so...
I don't understand it.
Why do all these terrible things always
have to happen whenever you're around?
Why did Mr.
Wolfwood have to die?
Who is he?
You must tell me now!
You heard about it.
You have to tell me!
I am to blame.
It's because of me that friends die.
They all got involved because of me.
I'm sorry, but that's why
you can't stay with me.
I asked you an important question,
and I expect a decent answer.
I need to understand!
Please, for once, I need
you to be honest with me!
As long as he lives, I
could never die honorably.
As long as Knives is alive.
Who's Knives?
My brother, I'm sorry to say.
-
Well that's it, now I need to spend.
spend a little time alone, okay?
And besides, there's a girl in pain who
could really use your support right now.
All this time...
Are you sure?
I mean, don't you want to follow him?
Frankly, I'm glad that?
No good troublemaker is gone,
let's get the report in quick
and get them to take us off!
this detail once and for all.
There's so many better things out there.
Besides, we don't
have enough lives.
I can handle it, Meryl. But you?
Unless we go after him now,
there's a good possibility that we may
never see him again in this lifetime.
Is that all right
with you, Meryl? Hmm?
I'm completely, totally,
perfectly fine now.
In fact, I need to get up and go.
And besides, as we both know, if
we don't work, we don't get paid.
Millie.
All right, first things first.
Do you have any idea which way he went?
Yes.
Great, then.
We have nothing to worry about.
I'll be ready in a few minutes.
Gather all of your things
together, too, Meryl.
Make sure you don't leave a thing behind
because we won't have time to come back.
Yes, of course.
Hey!
This guy's crying!
Yeah, and he's a grown-up!
Is there something wrong with that?
Everyone feels like crying sometimes.
Why are you crying?
A friend of mine went away,
and I'm sad. Why? Because...
He died because of you, didn't he?
It was your fault.
You're the one who
killed Wolf, aren't you?
Yeah, if you hadn't swayed him with your
stupid ideas, he might have had a chance.
You know that's true,
he didn't have to die.
What are you saying?
I decided to do this as my humble way of
exhibiting grief for the
loss of a good friend.
How'd I do you again?
Damn you are you going to draw?
Please stop don't do it someone else will
die if you do this another one will die
That's right, you can't possibly draw
You seem to think you've
never killed anyone,
but I'm afraid you're very sadly
mistaken You've managed to fool no one,
but yourself
You want to believe
that because your hands
aren't dirty because you didn't personally
pull the trigger that
you are innocent when
in actuality you've
killed countless people,
including the gung-ho guns and
your friend, Nicholas D. Wolfwood.
I was forced to do that!
I had no choice!
Every time you make
that face, it's strange.
My left arm begins to
shake uncontrollably.
Because it happens to be the very arm?
that attached your arm to your body.
I will be waiting for you on that hill.
If you wish to shoot me now, go ahead.
What happened?
My head feels funny.
What the hell?
How dare you?
How dare you be so damn casual
to toy with people's lives?
You do the same thing.
You alone turned July
and Augusta to rubble
and put a huge hole in
the fifth moon as well.
You can deny it, but you're a monster.
You and he are exactly the same breed.
Who do you think you are?
I'm the Thou Gung-Ho Gun,
Mid-Valley the Horn Freak.
The man who plays the greatest
music on the greatest stage of all.
It's time to play.
Join me on a number.
Won't you, Vash the Stampede?
Vash the Stampede? Oh,
no. No way. It can't be.
HELLO!
ORCHESTRAL SAVE
możemy!
Whoa!
What the...
Somehow he's able to
synchronize the sound waves
from his horn with the
physical sensation of pain.
Hmm, Sylvia is responding
rather well today.
Hey, you wouldn't know,
but up close,
the sound that's produced
by even a famous top-quality
instrument can actually
sound rather flat sometimes.
Of course, there are varying degrees,
but you are the only one able
to bring out the greatest sound.
A beautiful melody is
greeted with applause.
The audience shouts with appreciation.
The acknowledgement of
a splendid performance.
Why didn't you finish me off?
What are you waiting for?
It's obvious you could
have taken me out by now.
The answer is simple.
I'm under his orders.
The choice is not mine.
Knives.
Can't defy him.
Anyone working for Knives
is at his beck and call.
You relinquish all
rights and free thought.
End of discussion.
You're wrong.
You're wrong about that!
A superior being trying to show mercy?
Help me! I...
I can't stop myself!
Oh, no!
What's happening to me?
Legato again.
Oh, no! Please!
Jesus, Rey, don't kill me!
Somebody help! Stop me!
Please, help me!
Well, that's it.
Now I need to spend a
little time alone, okay?
Don't start brooding, Meryl.
It's a waste of time and energy.
And besides, you'll regret
it later, so just stop.
You're right, you're right,
you're absolutely right!
This is no time to lose my nerve.
Gotta keep going, right?
Meryl, let's go!
Are you all right?
Here, drink some water.
Talk about iron will.
Your dedication is commendable.
It's not over yet.
The show must go on.
Stop it!
You gotta be cool.
Arrgh!
Damn!
My B-flat!
My B-flat's gone!
Sorry, the show's over.
What are you saying?
You've been trying for
a ricochet shot? Hm.
Maybe, but it's not quite
time for the curtain call yet.
I have to accept this as my fate.
The destiny of the dying. Don't! Stop it!
If you shoot now!
Don't! No!
Legato!
We should have died a very
long time ago, you and I.
The instant we fell upon this sandy
land without pain and without sorrow.
Now the schedule has merely been set back.
The end is near.
It is time to embrace it.
That is why I must...
I must end it.
End it now.
No.
This is the climax, Vash the star.
So do you hate me?
I'm not surprised.
If you do, I wouldn't blame you.
So many sad things happen to you.
Whether they are friend or
enemy, the people you meet die.
It's enough to sap one's tears.
Shut up!
You know this is not finished yet.
Did you really expect the
end to come so easily?
Don't you understand you're not human?
It is time to realize exactly who you are.
It can't be!
There is power in that light.
Power that you have always possessed.
Even more, this represents what you are.
I...
I can't...
Not again...
NOT AGAIN!
Haven't you given up yet, Vash?
It's really quite annoying.
Bastard!
You're out of options.
Fight back or you'll die.
Why don't you go ahead?
I would welcome this to be my time.
After all,
there's no reason for such
an egocentric and complete
life like mine to be
allowed to continue anyway.
Give me the gift of nothingness.
Give me death.
My master is waiting for you.
He's looking forward to your visit.
I was compelled to attach
this arm to myself.
I had to because you
refused to be by his side.
Kill me.
I can't.
Go ahead.
I can't!
Millie!
Stop them!
No more!
I said stop it now!
And shoot me!
It's alright. Kill me.
It's simple.
All you need do is pull the trigger.
Once you have killed me,
this will all be over.
Come on.
Time to choose.
You have free will stop
it don't make me shoot.
Your faith is hopelessly obstinate
to actually believe the prattlings
of a woman who speaks in idealistic
terms that are worthless.
I guess that kind of
thinking is reasonable
for someone who's lived
for more than a century.
But that that way of life
is pathetic and comical.
Rem savor A wasted existence who
only spoke in aggravating logic.
A worthless human being.
Just like me, but unlike you.
That's enough!
Luck and persistence won't work forever.
As we journey through our lives,
we must always search for
ways to make everyone happy.
Don't force your way of life upon others.
No one has the right to
take the life of another.
Don't tell me your dreams
in a world like this!
If you keep your vision clear,
you will always find the future.
I understand.
Master, bash the Stampede, you will
experience eternal pain and suffering.
I don't know.
Thank
you.
I'll see you
next time.
NO!
I was dreaming, Rem.
Everything was so horribly dry.
There on that planet.
Even people's hearts.
As I watched the people who
lived there from far away,
I kept wondering why they went on living.
How they kept on living.
Rem.
Listen to me, Rem.
I did a bad thing.
Tell me, what should I do?